David M. Stowe Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Resource Files: ABCFM/UCBWM Geographical / Topical Files, 1810-1990s; Series VI
  - Geographically arranged material
    - Asia
      - India
        - Individuals
          - Cook, Margit: "It's All There", 1981 (Box 81, Folder 213)
          - Devapragasam, Samuel: Correspondence, 1941-1943 (Box 81, Folder 214)
          - Gaikwal, Ratnakar Hariba, 1940 (Box 81, Folder 215)
          - Gass, Jacob: "Saint With a Smile", 1962 (Box 81, Folder 216)
          - Goetsch, Frederick: "A Tribute", 1947 (Box 81, Folder 217)
          - Hall, Gordon, 1821-1939 (Box 81, Folder 218)
          - Hivale, Dr. Bhaskar: Research, 1955, n.d. (Box 81, Folder 219)
          - Keithahn, Dick (Mr. and Mrs.), 1834-1988 (Box 81, Folder 220)
          - Vaughan, Rev. Charles and Dr. Harriet: Medals from India Government, 1911,1937 (Box 81, Folder 221)
          - Newell, Samuel: Letter to future wife Philonela, 1979-1982 n.d. (Box 81, Folder 222)
          - Niles, Dr. D.T.: Death announcements, correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 81, Folder 223)
          - Power, Manorama, 1950-1954 (Box 81, Folder 224)
          - Prakash, Bhonsle: Research, 1950-1956 (Box 81, Folder 225)
          - Rahbar, David: Collection of reference letters for award, 1963-1989 (Box 82, Folder 226)
          - Rahuri, Marathi, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 227)
          - Thomas, Ross and Margaret: "Letters from India", 1928-1989 (Box 82, Folder 228)
        - Institutions
          - Ahmednagar College / Centre for Studies in Rural Development, 1944-1975 (Box 82, Folder 229-231)
          - American Board institutions, 1905-1990, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 232-233)
          - American Board Hospital for Women: Research, 1947-1949 (Box 82, Folder 234)
          - American College: Research, 1944-1947 (Box 83, Folder 235)
          - American Mission Boys School, 1949,1952 (Box 83, Folder 236)
          - American Mission Girls School, 1940-1944 (Box 83, Folder 237)
          - American Mission High School: Photographs, 1935 (Box 83, Folder 238)
          - Birdsnet Orphanage, n.d. (Box 83, Folder 239)
          - Boarding School: Booklets, writings, 1947-1957 (Box 83, Folder 240)
          - Boarding School in Aruppukottai, 1961,n.d. (Box 83, Folder 241)
          - Capron Hall Training School, 1935-1953 (Box 83, Folder 242)
          - Christian Service in Action, 1967-1969 (Box 83, Folder 243)
          - Church of South India: Research, 1946-1961 (Box 83, Folder 244)
          - Dadar School for the Blind, 1953,n.d. (Box 83, Folder 245)
          - Dayupuram Hospital and Home for Lepers (Box 83, Folder 246)
          - Gass Memorial Centre, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 247)
          - Hospitals and colleges, 1964-1964 n.d. (Box 84, Folder 248)
          - Kodaikanal School, 1941-1959 (Box 84, Folder 249)
          - Lady Doak College: Correspondence, pamphlets, booklets, reports, 1948-1968 (Box 84, Folder 250)
          - Lady Doak College: Photographs, 1969-1970 (Box 84, Folder 251)
          - Lady Doak College: Scrapbook of photos and letters, 1948 (Box 84, Folder 252)
          - Lucy Perry Noble Institute: Pamphlets, photos, 1921-1948 (Box 84, Folder 253)
          - Ludhiana Christian Medical College, 1962-1963 n.d. (Box 84, Folder 254)
          - Medical College research, 1948-1974 (Box 84, Folder 255)
          - Missions Council of the Congregational Christian Churches, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 256)
          - Nagpada Neighborhood House: Research, 1950-1964 (Box 85, Folder 257)
          - Pasumalai Schools, 1942-1950 (Box 85, Folder 258)
          - Pierce Memorial School and Hospital, 1940-1951 (Box 85, Folder 259)
          - St. Christian's Training College, 1941-1944 (Box 85, Folder 260)
          - Sisal Fiber Industry, 1954-1955 (Box 85, Folder 261)
          - Tirumangalam Board School/ Training School, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 262)
          - United Theological College, 1952-1971 (Box 85, Folder 263)
          - Willis F. Pierce Memorial Hospital, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 264)
          - Women's Christian College, 1941-1943 (Box 85, Folder 265)
          - World Health Organization "Health By the People", 1975 (Box 85, Folder 266)
        - Topical
          - Evangelical, 1926-1958 (Box 85, Folder 267)
          - Medical issues, 1954-1955 n.d. (Box 85, Folder 268)
          - Medical issues, evangelical missions, 1960-1968 n.d. (Box 85, Folder 269)
          - Meeting minutes, pamphlets, 1962-1964 (Box 85, Folder 270)
          - Memorial papers of the American Marathi Mission, 1882 (Box 86, Folder 271)
          - Missions, 1950s (Box 86, Folder 272)
          - Missions, national church leaders, reports, 1947-1997, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 273-276)
          - Satara research, 1953-1961 (Box 86, Folder 277)
          - Sholapurplace, 1934-1950 (Box 86, Folder 278)
          - Valdala: Historical, 1952-1962 (Box 86, Folder 279)
          - Pamphlets, brochures, 1968 (Box 177, Folder 18-19)
        - Photographs
          - Colleges, locals: Slides, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 280)
          - Missionaries and locals, photos and slides, 1950-1972, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 281-284)
          - Tibetan refugees, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 285)
      - Indonesia
        - Makasser Theological Seminary, 1956-1961 (Box 87, Folder 286)
        - Satya Watyana University, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 287)
        - Historical, missionaries, 1954-1974 (Box 87, Folder 288-289)
      - Japan
        - Individuals
          - Buma, Kentaro, 1949-1951 (Box 87, Folder 290)
          - Fiyishino, Taizo, 1949 (Box 87, Folder 291)
          - Jones, Leroy Lansing: "Leroy Lansing Jones and the American Board" and "L..L. Jones in Japan", 1975,n.d. (Box 87, Folder 292)
          - Putna, Cliff, 1999.n.d. (Box 87, Folder 293)
          - Takami, Toshihiro, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 294)
        - Institutions
          - Baika High School and College, 1948 (Box 87, Folder 295)
          - Colleges and schools, 1912-1973 (Box 87, Folder 296)
          - Consulate General of Japan: "Facts about Japan", 1966 (Box 87, Folder 297)
          - Doshisha University, 1958-1995 (Box 87, Folder 298)
          - Glory Kindergarten, Shoei Junior College, 1949-1950 (Box 88, Folder 299)
          - International Christian University, incl. photographs, 1948-1959 (Box 88, Folder 300-301)
          - Japan Missions of the American Board, 1915-1992 (Box 88, Folder 302-303)
          - Japan Missions of the American Board, n.d. (Box 177, Folder 21)
          - Junan High School (Matsuyama Night School), Orlinda Girls Pierce Shool (Shinonma Girls School), 1931-1953 (Box 88, Folder 304)
          - Loving All Institution (The), etc., 1960 (Box 88, Folder 305)
          - Miyagi College Research, 1957-1958 (Box 88, Folder 306)
          - Alumnae Association of Miyagi Gakuin, Sendai, Japan, 1995 (Box 177, Folder 20)
          - Morioka Christian Education Center, 1966 (Box 88, Folder 307)
          - Nishinomiya Kobe College, 1935-1953, 1997 (Box 88, Folder 308-309)
          - Okinawa Interboard Committee, 1960s (Box 88, Folder 310)
          - Seujatsu Gakuen Junior College, Seikatsu Gakuen High School, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 311)
          - Tsurukawa Center, 1955-1975 (Box 89, Folder 312)
          - United Church of Christ in Japan, 1962-1963 (Box 89, Folder 313)
          - Yodagawa Neighborhood House, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 314)
        - Topical
          - Committee minutes, reports, correspondence, etc., 1958-1974 (Box 89, Folder 315-316)
          - Gulick Friendship Dolls, songs from Japan, 1997,n.d. (Box 89, Folder 317)
          - Missions, missionaries, etc., 1941-1991 (Box 89, Folder 318-319)
          - Okayawa: Historical, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 320)
          - Pamphlets, reports, 1947-1957, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 321-322)
        - Photographs
          - Church officials, members, locala, 1934-1962 (Box 90, Folder 323-324)
          - "Faces and places", 1952-1961 (Box 90, Folder 325)
          - Japan Interboard Meeting, 1962-1965 (Box 90, Folder 326)
          - Kagawa locals, 1948 (Box 90, Folder 327)
          - Schools, buildings, locals, 1963-1974 (Box 90, Folder 328)
          - Stewardship Council, 1956,n.d. (Box 90, Folder 329)
      - Korea
        - Missions, missionaries, local leaders, 1956,1961,n.d. (Box 90, Folder 330)
      - Nepal
        - Photographs: Sherpa nurses, 1972,n.d. (Box 90, Folder 332)
      - Pakistan
        - Refugees, 1962-1971 (Box 90, Folder 333)
      - Philippines
        - Individuals
          - Laubach, Frank C., 1984,n.d. (Box 90, Folder 334)
          - Laubach, Frank C., 1984 (Box 177, Folder 22)
          - Rodriguez, Proculo, 1950,1961 (Box 90, Folder 335)
          - van Victor, Lloyd and Maisie: Lloyd's kidnap, Maisie's death, 1977-1979 (Box 90, Folder 336)
        - Institutions
          - American Board in Mindanao, other missions, 1950-1990 (Box 90, Folder 337)
          - Brokenshire Memorial Hospital, 1948-1964 (Box 90, Folder 338)
          - Churches, organizations, 1939-1955 (Box 91, Folder 339)
          - Dansalan Junior College, 1952-1979 (Box 91, Folder 340)
          - Department of Public Welfare of the United Church of Christ:: "Church and Community" magazine, 1961-1962 (Box 91, Folder 341)
          - Silliman University, 1948-1955 (Box 91, Folder 342)
          - Southern Christian College, 1950-1952 (Box 91, Folder 343-344)
          - United Church of Christ, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 345)
        - Topical
          - Historical, 1949-1964 (Box 91, Folder 346-347)
      - Sri Lanka
        - Photographs: Girls college, Bishop, 1971-1972 1979 (Box 91, Folder 348)
      - Taiwan
        - American Board, United Church, 1961-1965 (Box 91, Folder 349)
      - Tibet
        - "Ministry to Tibetan Refugees", n.d. (Box 91, Folder 350)
      - Vietnam
        - Missions, 1966-1968 (Box 91, Folder 351)
    - Australia
      - King, Edwin: Correspondence, 1956 (Box 92, Folder 352)
    - Europe
      - General
        - History, priority paper, 1968,n.d. (Box 92, Folder 353)
          - Missions, 1946-1963 (Box 92, Folder 354)
      - Austria
        - UCBWM: UCBWM information sheet, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 355)
      - Bulgaria
        - Research files, 1929-1990 (Box 92, Folder 356)
      - Czechoslovakia
        - Zelinka, Paul A. (Mrs.): Correspondence, etc., 1979-1982 (Box 92, Folder 357)
        - American Board: Missions, 1945-1954 (Box 92, Folder 358)
        - Biographies of Czechoslovakian church founders in Czechoslovakian language, 1979-1981 (Box 92, Folder 359)
      - France
        - Le College Cevenol: Chambon-Sur- Lignon, 1955-1964 (Box 92, Folder 360)
        - L'Accull Fraternal: Research, 1947-1965 (Box 92, Folder 361)
      - Germany
        - Rev. and Mrs. Robert Starbuck: Research (Mainz-Kastel), 1958-1961 (Box 92, Folder 362)
        - Research files, 1953-1970 (Box 92, Folder 363)
      - Greece
        - American Board: Missions, 1928-1949 n.d. (Box 92, Folder 364)
        - Anatolia College: Research, 1946-1958 (Box 93, Folder 365)
        - Orlinda Girls/ Childs Pierce College, 1932-1969, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 366-368)
        - Research files, 1952-1963 n.d. (Box 93, Folder 369)
      - Italy
        - Santi, Teofilo Dr.: Research, 1952-1960 (Box 94, Folder 370)
        - "Casa Mia", 1954-1973 (Box 94, Folder 371)
        - Historical documentation, 1953-1954 (Box 94, Folder 372)
        - Photographs: refugees, 1955 (Box 94, Folder 373)
      - Spain
        - L' Etoile du Matin", 1997 (Box 94, Folder 374)
        - Research files, 1949-1958 (Box 94, Folder 375)
    - Latin America
      - Brazil
        - Missions article, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 376)
      - Ecuador
        - Research files, 1955-1965 (Box 94, Folder 377)
      - Guadalajara
        - Photos: "Gigantes", local churches, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 378)
      - Haiti
        - Missions, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 379)
      - Honduras
        - Communications and Media: Reports, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 380)
        - Missions, 1959-1968 (Box 94, Folder 381-382)
        - Slides, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 383)
      - Mexico
        - American Board: Missions in Mexico, Honduras and Ecuador, 1944-1971 (Box 95, Folder 384)
        - Concilio Congregacional de Mexico, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 385)
        - Congregacional Church of Mexico: History, 1951-1957 (Box 95, Folder 386)
        - Missions, 1946-1969, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 387-389)
        - Photos: Church members, school children, 1959-1962 (Box 95, Folder 391-392)
        - Scrapbooks, incl. re. Activities of Centros Culturales, Jazmin y Gigantes, 1979-1980,n.d. (Box 95, Folder 393-394)
        - Junta General de Iglesias Congregacionales de Mexico, 1960,1965 (Box 177, Folder 23)
      - Nicaragua
        - Photos of missionaries, local area churches, 1980 (Box 96, Folder 395)
      - Uruguay
        - "Background Information" Communication on Missionary Education, 1958 (Box 96, Folder 396)
    - Near East
      - General
        - Missions, 1950-1969, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 397-398)
        - Pamphlets, information from Fred Field Goodsell, 1969,1970, n.d. (Box 177, Folder 24-25)
      - Armenia
        - Missions, reports, newspaper clippings, 1895-1991 (Box 96, Folder 399-400)
      - Iraq
        - Research files, 1957-1962 (Box 96, Folder 401)
      - Jordan
        - Pamphlets, 1953-1966 (Box 96, Folder 402)
      - Lebanon
        - The American University of Beirut, 1965-1966 (Box 96, Folder 403)
        - The Near Eastern School of Theology, 1968-1970 (Box 96, Folder 404)
        - Research files, 1953-1966 (Box 97, Folder 405)
      - Pakistan
        - "Current News of the Church Overseas", 1964 (Box 97, Folder 406)
      - Palestine
        - American Board: Missions, refugees, 1950, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 407)
        - Photos: refugees, 1979 (Box 97, Folder 408)
      - Syria
        - Tuers, Elizabeth: Correspondence, 1954 (Box 97, Folder 409)
        - Aleppo College: Pamphlets, photos, 1949-1962 (Box 97, Folder 410-411)
        - Aleppo College Brief No. 1, 1932 (Box 178, Folder 26)
        - American Board, etc., 1958-1963 (Box 97, Folder 412)
        - American High School for Girls, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 413)
        - Protestant College in Beirut: "Views of the Syrian Protestant College Beirut", 1945 (Box 97, Folder 414)
        - Photos: American Board tree planting ceremony, 1949 (Box 97, Folder 415)
      - Turkey
        - Missions, 1944-1964 (Box 97, Folder 416)
        - Antab, Ghasi, 1889,1917 (Box 97, Folder 417)
        - Blake, Mr. and Mrs.: Report, correspondence, 1978 (Box 97, Folder 418)
        - Blakney, Charles Rev.: Sermons, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 419)
        - Ely, Charlotte: Correspondence, 1991 (Box 97, Folder 420)
        - Erickson, Charles T.: "My Retreat from Civilization", 1968 (Box 97, Folder 421)
        - Hamline, Cyrus: Life story, 1900-1999 (Box 97, Folder 422)
        - Hemingway, Isabel: Correspondence, 1950-1967 (Box 97, Folder 423)
        - Jesusist groups, 1971-1975 (Box 97, Folder 424)
        - Lovatt, Ethel: Correspondence, 1952-1968 (Box 98, Folder 425)
        - Merrill, John Ernest: Manuscript, 1955 (Box 98, Folder 426)
        - Nolan, Myrtle: Correspondence, etc., 1922-1991 (Box 98, Folder 427)
        - Nute, Cy: Correspondence, writings, 1957-1980 (Box 98, Folder 428)
        - Perry, Edward T., 1919-1936 (Box 98, Folder 429)
        - Smith, F.O.: "A Hawkeye Abroad", n.d. (Box 98, Folder 430)
        - Stowe, David M.: Correspondence,etc., 1963-1970 (Box 98, Folder 431)
        - Wood, Rev. George W.: Correspondence, etc., 1900-1961 (Box 98, Folder 432)
        - Wright, Lester James, 1982-1983 n.d. (Box 98, Folder 433)
        - American Academy for Girls, 1945-1970 (Box 98, Folder 434)
        - American Board: Bulletins, etc., 1919-1978 (Box 98, Folder 435)
        - American Board schools, missions, 1948-1976 (Box 98, Folder 436-441)
        - American Clinic, 1946-1951 (Box 99, Folder 442)
        - American Collegiate Institute: Schools, 1961-1967 (Box 99, Folder 443)
        - American School for Boys, 1947,1954 (Box 99, Folder 444)
        - Azariah Smith Memorial Hospital, 1947-1972 (Box 99, Folder 445)
        - Colleges, 1968-1981 (Box 99, Folder 446)
        - Hospitals: Tale Nute Clinic, 1955-1960 (Box 99, Folder 447)
        - Istanbul Biblehouse, 1972-1988 (Box 99, Folder 448)
        - Red House Press and other publications, 1968-1994 (Box 100, Folder 449-450)
        - Tarsus American College, 1950-1964 (Box 100, Folder 451)
        - United Church Board for World Ministries, 1919-1979 (Box 100, Folder 452)
        - Missions history, 1855-1964 (Box 100, Folder 453-458)
        - National church leaders, 1937,1959 1978 (Box 100, Folder 459)
        - Protestant Missionary Movement (The), 1920-1969 (Box 100, Folder 460)
        - Carleton, Alford: "The Developmen of Missionary Policy in Turkey", 1930 (Box 178, Folder 28)
        - Photo album, 1958 (Box 101, Folder 461)
        - Photos: Marash schools, etc., 1909-1945 (Box 101, Folder 462)
    - North America
      - General
        - Cherokee Studies, 1979-1980 (Box 101, Folder 463)
      - Hawaii
        - Obookiah, Henry, 1967-1995 (Box 101, Folder 464)
        - Missions history, 1956-1995 (Box 101, Folder 465-467)
        - Brochure, n.d. (Box 178, Folder 29)
      - Virginia
        - Axtell, James: "Some thoughts on the Ethnohistory of Missions", 1982 (Box 101, Folder 468)
    - Oceania /Micronesia
      - Wilson, Eleanor, 1956-1957 (Box 101, Folder 469)
      - Missions, research files, 1910-1991 (Box 101, Folder 470-472)
      - Photos: Locals, schools, 1960-1980 (Box 101, Folder 473)
      - Photos: Morning Star: boat, missionary crew members, 1947 (Box 101, Folder 474)
  - Resource files: Topically arranged
    - Andover controversy and the ABCFM, 1943 Mar (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Archives at Harvard/ Andover, 1943-1968, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Archives at Harvard; Microfilming, 1982-1999 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Archives in Lancaster, 1982, 1995 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Biblical Witness fellowship, 1983 Sep-1984 Apr (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Black manifesto incident; James Forman, 1969, 1971, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Blacks and missions, 1971, 1989, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Board history; "The ABCFM's Philosophy of Missions in the 19th Century" by Kazuo Shiono, 1999-2003 (Box 179, Folder 30)
    - Board minutes; Indexing, 1962 Aug 20 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Christian Church (Disciples of Christ), 1989 Sep. 29, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Christian Church (Disciples of Christ)/ United Christian Missionary Society; Proposed merger with UCBWM, 1969-1970 May (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Christian Church (Disciples of Christ)/ United Christian Missionary Society; Proposed merger with UCBWM, 1970 Jun-Nov (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Christian Church (Disciples of Christ)/ United Christian Missionary Society; Proposed merger with UCBWM, 1971-1978, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Christian Church (Disciples of Christ)/ UBCWM; Common Global Ministries Board, 1994, 1997 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - The Christian Church in the U.nited States, 1919-1928 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - The Christian Church in the United States, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Christian Higher Education Fund, 1958-1962 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Church Board relations, 1871-1983 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Committee on Interpretation, 1961-1962 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Congregational Christian Service Committee, 1943-1946 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Congregational Christian Service Committee, 1947-1952 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Congregational Christian Service Committee, 1955-1981, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Congregational Library Boston; inventory of ABCFM materials, 1968-1999, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Conversations with pastors in New England re; missions, 1935-1936 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - Conversion/ cultural change, 1987, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Corporate membership, 1930, 1968-1969 (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - Corporate social responsibility, 1974-1987 (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - Decision making processes, 1966-1985, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 27)
    - Dialogue with other religions, 1974, 1981 (Box 104, Folder 28)
    - Ecology, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 29)
    - Ecumenical relationships, 1968 -1995 (Box 104, Folder 30)
    - Educational mission, 1967, 1976, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 31)
    - Evangelical and Reformed Church; Board of International Missions, 1956-1963 (Box 104, Folder 32)
    - Evangelical and Reformed Church; Board of International Missions (Box 105, Folder 33)
    - Evangelical and Reformed Church; Board of International Missions (Box 105, Folder 34)
    - Evangelical and Reformed Church; Board of International Missions; Sketches of missionaries, 1938, 1949, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 35)
    - Evangelical and Reformed Church missions; History, 1949-1994 (Box 105, Folder 36)
    - Evangelical and Reformed Church; World Service Division, 1941-1980, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 37)
    - Evangelical and Reformed Church; Merger to form UCBWM, 1957-1959 (Box 105, Folder 38)
    - Evangelical Synod, 1937, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 39)
    - Evangelical Synod; Board of International Missions of the Evangelical and Reformed Church, 1934-1937 (Box 179, Folder 31)
    - Evangelical Synod; Board of International Missions of the Evangelical and Reformed Church, 1941-1982 (Box 179, Folder 32)
    - Evangelicals, 1978, 1982 (Box 105, Folder 40)
    - Evangelische Kirche Union, 1981-1983 (Box 105, Folder 41)
    - Evangelism, 1964-1988 (Box 179, Folder 33)
    - Evangelism; Life of the Church Committee, 1967 (Box 106, Folder 42)
    - Evangelism/ UCBWM, 1956-1972 (Box 106, Folder 43)
    - Evangelism/ UCBWM, 1973-1979 (Box 106, Folder 44)
    - Evangelism/ UCBWM, 1981-1991, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 45)
    - Fellowship of Continuing Understanding and Support (Focus), 1973, 1991-2002 (Box 106, Folder 46)
    - Fellowship of Continuing Understanding and Support (Focus) (Box 106, Folder 47)
    - Fellowship of Those Who Care, 1930-1946 (Box 106, Folder 48)
    - Financial statistics UCBWM, 1910-1979 (Box 106, Folder 49)
    - Financial statistics UCBWM, 1980-1984 (Box 106, Folder 50)
    - Financial statistics UCBWM, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 51)
    - German Congregational Churches, 1938-1987, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 52)
    - Goodsell, Fred Field; Record of interviews; missionaries, staff, miscellaneous, 1930 (Box 107, Folder 53)
    - Goodsell, Fred Field; "Seekers for the Way of Life, With special reference to The Continuation of the Christian-Muslim Dialogue", 1970 (Box 107, Folder 54)
    - Goodsell, Fred Field: Chronological Highlights of American Board History, 1842-1861, 1963 (Box 107, Folder 55)
    - Goodsell, Fred Field: American Board history projects, autobiography, 1910-1975, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 56)
    - Goodsell, Fred Field: Hawaii mission of ABCFM, 1955 (Box 107, Folder 57)
    - Goodsell, Fred Field: Miscellaneous, 1920-1980 (Box 179, Folder 34)
    - History of UCC; Predessors, misc., 1985, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 58)
    - Human rights, 1976-1982 (Box 107, Folder 59)
    - Hunger program, 1978-1985, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 60)
    - Illustrations for proposed history of Board, 1939,1976, n.d. (Box 107, Folder 61)
    - Imperialism, 1953-1998 (Box 107, Folder 62)
    - Indigenization, 1928-1998 (Box 107, Folder 63)
    - Internationalization of Board, 1973-1974, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 64)
    - International Seminars program, 1956-1963 (Box 108, Folder 65)
    - James Foundation of New York, Inc., 1952-1964 (Box 108, Folder 66)
    - Leadership training, 1971-1974, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 67)
    - Library at New York office, 1985-1992, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 68)
    - Life of the Church Committee, UCBWM, 1962-1969, n.d. (Box 108, Folder 69)
    - London Missionary Society, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 70)
    - Lyon, Mary, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 71)